altamiraweb.com 2011-05-28

# Privacy — Altamira Recruitment and Employee management software

Our policy regarding the handling of personal data 

## Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) sets out the basis on which Altamira Srl (“Altamira”) may process your personal data. As used in this Policy, the term “personal data” has the meaning given to it in applicable data protection legislation and includes, but is not limited to, your name, contact details, compensation details, CV information, and other such information we may collect in accordance with this Policy when you use Altamira’s website (“Site”) or send e-mails to one of Altamira’s e-mail addresses. Please note that other websites or services that may be affiliated with Altamira may be subject to different privacy policies. This Policy is compliant with the EC Data Protection Directive (95/46/EC). 

## Applicability

Altamira respects your privacy and believes that all personal data should be used responsibly and appropriately. In general, you may visit the Site anonymously and without revealing any personal data. However, when you request information from us using one of the request forms and/or enroll in a trial of our platform, we collect certain personal data. By requesting information and/or registering for a trial, you indicate your agreement with the terms of this Policy and consent to the processing of your personal data as specified in this Policy. Altamira may transfer your personal data to those countries where servers supporting the Site are located. 

## How personal data is collected?

Altamira collects your personal data through the Site and e-mails you may send to Altamira’s e-mail addresses. 

## Who may access your information?

The personal data you upload when using the Site or provide to Altamira by e-mail will be used in conjunction with Altamira’s sales or technical support services. Altamira may use subcontractors to manage and provide these services and may therefore be required to share your personal data with such subcontractors. 

## What information is collected?

Personal data collected may include, but is not limited to, your name, contact details, and other information you may provide to us through the Site or by e-mail. 

## Cookie policy

The Site uses cookies to associate user sessions with their data. By default the cookies are temporary (so called “session cookies”) and are not stored on your computer. This Policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and beyond the control of Altamira. 

## Changes to the Policy

Altamira may change this Policy or modify or withdraw access to the Site without notice. 

Corporate Information Altamira Srl.  
Corso Magenta, 56  
20124 Milano  
Italy
